I went out on the track to drive a
Lamborghini and also had a
chat with the company's uncle,
Stephan Winkelman.  I was at the
historic Imola circuit, where I do
n't think I've ever seen so many
Lamborghinis all together.  There was also
the historic Kuntage made iconic by the film
The Wolf of Wall Street.  But I wasn't there
by accident.  First I drove a
Lamborghini Urus during the parade on the
track, accompanied by my prodz and then
we moved on to the road where we
drove a splendid Lamborghini
Revelto whizzing around the curves of the hills
around Imola.  Excuse me, sorry, what
job do you do to afford that plane?
Buy my course.  At that point I
returned to the track directly on the grid
to watch the start of
the Super Trofeo race.  After leaving,
I went to see some of
Lamborghini's most iconic historical models and
finally sat down with my friend Stephan
Winkelman in front of a spectacular
Lamborghini phenomenon.
In all these years of experience at
Lamborghini, what is the most
difficult moment?  Of course, it was the whole
post-Covid period, we had to decide
which was the right product, whether
combustion, hybrid or electric.
[music] There have been many
moments with the hybrid where we had some
imbalances [music] or moments where
we thought it couldn't work.
Of course, for a small brand it's
important to invest in things that
make the difference, and that was the hybrid
because we didn't have the money to make both
the hybrid and the combustion engine and
the electric one.  It is very important to have
clarity on the product range,
technology and derivatives.
In your opinion, is the customer ready for
full electric?  Ours today tells us
that since we don't sell mobility but
we sell dreams, your segment must
remain exciting or emotional and for
this I also want the sound of the
commission engine.
You see it in both Italian and
foreign customers, perhaps on a
global level.
In your opinion, what characteristics are
necessary to do your job well?   It
takes passion and discipline, a
certain ability to resist stress.
The customer.  But how did it happen in all
these years that you lived at
Lamborghini?
It's gotten younger, there are
many more of them.  I accumulate all the
fact of Made in Italy that love
sports cars, they are entrepreneurs.
If you had to give advice to your
beginning self,
what would you say?   Good thing I did
n't know what
awaited me
today.  What's your favorite thing about
your job and what's the thing you would
n't do [music] if you could?
Well, the favorite is when you have a
lot to do with the product.  What I
like least is when we have
long meetings on boring topics that need to be
addressed.
What is the second of the future of
Lamborghini cars?
The cars must remain exciting and
ultimately they must remain
dream cars.  We're already thinking about what
will happen in 4-5 years, which then has to
stay on the market for another 8 or nine.  I
only had 10 minutes, so if you want to
see the entire video where I spend the whole
day at the company and where my uncle
shows me around the entire production,
let me know in the comments.